Caesar was the son of Mario Zeppeli,
considered the best furniture
maker in all of Naples.
Mario was a proper Italian man of his
day, thoroughly dedicated to his family.
To Caesar, he was the ideal man.
When Caesar was ten, Mario suddenly
left without so much as a word.
Having lost their mother
years before, they were alone.
Distant relatives stole
what little they had.
Caesar became a delinquent, growing to hate
his father and what he had done to them.
I bet he's living carefree
with some hot young woman!
I'm gonna fight him and then kill him!
He threw away his youth and his future.
He committed theft, arson, assault,
anything short of outright murder.
Even the local mafiosos feared him.
Hey, you're that guy
named Caesar, aren't you?
So what's your last name?
I don't have one.
Well, that means there's
no way you're Italiano.
Italian are proud of their family names.
Never holding back,
he often started fights by using a wrench
to suddenly bash his opponent's head,
before calmly finishing them off.
Though he didn't know it yet, he
was already beginning to use Hamon.
Then, at age 16 in Rome...
There's no mistake.
It's really him.
At that moment, Caesar felt he
might murder his own father.
But then...
What is all that?
Huh?
That's a massive diamond.
No!
Boy, don't touch that stone!
It's you!
What the hell is the one doing?
Stay back!
This is all a trap!
Events had occurred 50 years ago that
were completely unknown to Caesar.
His grandfather, Will, had died
tragically while on an expedition.
Mario took up his father's torch
and trained with Hamon to prepare,
discovering the ruins soon after.
He began a worldwide search
for a way to defeat the
monsters within and unlock
the treasure they hide.
But Caesar knew none of this.
Young man, I beg from you a favor.
Make your way to Venice and
speak with a woman named Lisa.
Lisa, it's a matter of life and death.
She is the only one who has
any chance of stopping them.
Perhaps because so many years
had passed and Caesar had grown,
Mario did not recognize his son.
Caesar's father hadn't abandoned
his family for selfish reasons.
He'd left in order to keep his children
safe from the nightmare of the Pillar Men.
Father!
It's time for love to call it a true love
It's time for a moment to call it a true
love I
want to call
we're gonna get yasura no Seiko wo
tuk Dario Knight omoi ga Mili no kira ko
Like a burning stone Atsuko
like a burning stone Ketsu Mega
ni kizamareta yunan ni Uki
araru Granny hokori no kizuna
Nihiri shimete
I see.
Caesar's misunderstanding led to a
deep hatred, but then that changed.
It became pride in his
father and his family.
So Caesar sought me out and picked
up where his father had left off.
He's going because he
needs to avenge his father.
Forgive me, Caesar.
I didn't mean to speak
ill of your brave family.
If you still want to go
charging in there even
though you know damn well
it's going to be a trap,
then you must have figured
out some way to beat cars.
Changed my mind.
Since you're going in that derelict
hellhole, then I'm right behind you.
Caesar Zeppeli.
A set of footprints
leads into the mansion.
Oh, who was that?
I swear I saw someone there.
Am I hallucinating?
There it is!
It's not an illusion!
What the hell is that?
Seizure!
He vanished!
But I know he's here. Close.
He's within a few steps of me.
Does Kars have some kind of new trick? No.
The sun is shining too strong for him.
He can't be out here and survive.
The cat's stance, a
fundamental element of Kong fu.
Caesar has never heard of Kong fu,
but instinctively balances his
stance as he relaxes his limbs,
ready for attack from any direction.
For him, it is not a
technique, but a reflex.
Caesar!
What do you think you're doing?
Going in there all alone is madness.
Just stay back, Instructor!
I can't move at all,
let alone go rushing in.
Something is hiding just inside
the entrance of the building.
What do you mean I can't
see a thing in there?
A single footprint just appeared!
He must have jumped!
He's coming at us from above!
There!
What the...?
Wamuu!
Instructor, no!
What the hell is this?
That guy was Wamuu.
Are he and Kars inside
that mansion together?
But wait a minute.
How can Wamuu come outside during the day?
He did look kind of ghost-like.
Where is he?
That infuriating, smart-talking upstart?
I hear tell that Jojo
has learned quite a bit.
Where is the man who killed Master ACDC?
Wind.
Wamu can control the wind.
That's why he's difficult to see.
Air's coming from pipes in his chest.
He's only slightly
visible because of water
vapor swirling in the
flow around his body.
I've got it!
He's cloaking himself in vapor
that he's generating from the air.
And then he's pumping
it out of those pipes.
It's refracting light,
like a million tiny prisms.
It's a suit that bends light around
him, protecting him from the sun's rays?
thus allowing him to be outside.
That's why he seems to be transparent.
Too bad JoJo isn't here.
You are the bubble user
named Caesar, are you not?
Simply by looking into your eyes,
I can see that you've also
learned much through your ordeals.
Very well you are worthy of
death at my hands bubble user?
Let's see who dies I feel like I did
back then when I was naive and poor
back when you viciously took the
life of my father and now I'll use my
viciousness to destroy you very
impressive but don't think your wind
will be able to just blow my bubbles
away some bubbles go right through a
I've significantly updated my
grandfather's Hamon Cutter!
Bubble Cutter!
High-speed rotation turns the
bubbles into a salvo of deadly discs.
Hamon ensures they
won't pop along the way.
The wind protecting you is nothing more
than a pocket of empty air to them.
Instead of defending
you, it'll suck them in!
I underestimated his skill with Hamon.
It is far more than I bargained for.
Now, Hamon user! Hold it!
I won't let you go inside!
Gliding Bubble Cutter!
Now, while you're standing there
stunned and helplessly off balance,
I'll give you a Hamon kick!
But Caesar was in for
an extremely big shock.
If you are tripped,
you try your best not to fall,
Especially if you need to avoid
sunlight in order to survive.
But Wamuu was different.
He bent over backwards and attacked.
I've never seen anything like that before.
He's not just an immortal
with incredible strength.
With senses like that,
he's a fighting genius.
But my bubble cutter must have
inflicted severe damage on him.
The advantage here is mine!
I have a way to take
you down, even indoors!
My nerves are home to a razor's edge.
I can feel differences in the air.
I have the itch like when I was poor.
My breathing is relaxed and normal.
I'm not sweating.
Perfect Haman conditions.
Instructor Machina!
I see you've taken off your
coat and made yourself ready.
WAMU!
Damn it.
Caesar and Machina aren't here.
Do you think they might
have already gone inside?
No, that's his.
That's Machina's arm.
Now, take this!
Avalanche!
That's nothing.
Bubble Cutter!
Running?
I won't run or hide from you!
Bubble Cutter!
You're dead, Wamuu!
Riding Power Cutter!
Wamuu?
I'm finished with these games.
You're through.
Divine Sans!
Wait a minute, Wamuu!
Stop and look around!
Huh?
My bubble cutters are now bubble lenses,
and they're floating in
the air all around you.
And that enormous hole you
knocked in the wall earlier?
Is just like the open shutter of a camera.
on a bright summer day.
Those lenses, they focus the sunlight...
into the hotel!
You can't move.
You're like film, a frozen image!
You're totally exposed, Wamuu!
Trying your vapor barrier again?
Not this time!
Now, Wamuu, I'm going to finish you
off with a direct hormone blast!
One point, at one moment,
a tiny blind spot.
Caesar's body created the briefest of
shadows amid the blazing wall of sunlight.
Wamuu didn't waste his chance.
He showed Caesar once again
that he was a fighting genius!
And a genius of strategy! Wind power!
Divine sandstorm!
Such destruction!
It couldn't be!
It's Wamuu's divine
sandstorm, I'm sure of it!
So that means Caesar is...
You had grown so much in so little time
I'm satisfied I haven't had a fight?
Like that in ages now warrior
of Hamon and it was a close
one as well if the wind of
my divine sandstorm hadn't
had the strength to blow your
bubble senses to oblivion I
have no idea how I would have
stopped the light before it.
destroyed me.
And even if the mighty Lord
Kars, who cannot use wind,
had been the one to first note your
presence and confront you as I did,
and faced your power,
if he had prevailed, he most certainly
would have been in far worse shape?
than I find myself in now.
Enough.
You will not fight again, for you
have nothing left with which to fight.
My divine sandstorm has shredded your
body beyond any chance of survival.
Stop.
The battle is over.
You have no more harmone
with which to continue. See?
You've almost completely bled out.
That means you have no hope.
Stop, Caesar.
Goodbye.
Your life and all you once were has ended.
What?
My lip rang with the antidote.
Why did you take it?
I...
I'm not afraid to die here.
But I am a proud member
of the Zeppeli family.
So you see, it's in my blood.
Something like this might mean absolutely
nothing to a demented
inhuman monster like you.
My father didn't recognize me, but he
sacrificed his life to save mine anyway.
I, my grandfather,
gave his hormone energy to save Jojo's
grandfather right before he died.
It's tradition.
I have to do something.
I, I can't let my life's flame
just sputter out to darkness.
This is the Zeppeli family spirit,
handed down from the past to
ensure the family's future.
It's the human spirit.
Jojo!
This is the last of my hormones!
Take it from me!
Did you hear that?
It sounded like Caesar screaming!
Yes, I heard it!
Oh no, Caesar can't!
Caesar!
He made a bubble from his blood.
He must have used every last
bit of his Hamon to make it.
Before he died,
he saved it for his friends, rather
than using it to try and destroy me.
I let it go, but not because
I'm sentimental about him.
His talent as a fighter was undeniable.
He has my deep respect
as a fellow warrior.
I will hold you in the last moments we
spent together forever in my memory, Caesar.
A man as splendid and as fleeting
as the bubbles he conjured.
The place is a wreck.
A divine sandstorm did all this!
And Caesar was caught.
Right inside the heart of it.
A bubble.
Could it be?
Look at that.
Inside is Caesar's bandana.
Also, a ring.
Wamuu's lip ring.
This hormone energy feels really strange.
Whoa!
You know,
I haven't been able to
bring myself to call
Caesar's name since we made
our way into this place.
It's because I'm afraid
there'll be no answer.
If I came in here and cried out his name,
there might not be any response in return.
There might be nothing
but a lifeless silence.
That is what scares me.
I couldn't accept it, so
I didn't call his name.
But now, I know he's gone.
The halmon contained in that bubble
told me everything I needed to know.
Right here, just a few
moments ago, Caesar died.
Caesar, you bastard!
You had to be a damn show-off
right up until the very end!
And then you leave a precious
gift like this for me.
Caesar!
Where are you?
Where the hell are you sleeping?
I'll find you, Caesar!
I'll pick you up! Caesar!
Jojo!
This isn't the time to search or grieve.
We have work to do. What?
There are two of them and two of us.
The numbers are balanced.
They're even.
That trail of blood leading up the stairs
tells me that Caesar
significantly wounded Wamu.
We're in the middle of enemy territory.
Let's go finish this fight.
Jojo, come on.
Take the antidote.
Then we'll go hunt those bastards down.
That heartless...
She can't even manage to shed
a single tear for Caesar!
Coach Lisa Lisa, your cigarette.
It's backwards.
Lisa Lisa is our coach, so she
always has to keep a cool exterior.
I know she wants to cry,
much more than I do.
He treated her like a goddess, and
knew her longer than I've known her.
I have to try and hold my feelings back.
Caesar, I know you always thought
I was impulsive and self-centered
But sometimes I do understand
the feelings of those around me
I might finally be learning
I swear,
I will fight them both
like the devil until
there's nothing left of
them I'll avenge you,
Caesar Your spirit is with me
Blood.
His blood.
This is where he fell.
Caesar.
Caesar!
They were deep in enemy territory.
Cars and Wamu were very nearby, but the
two simply couldn't help themselves.
Jojo called out Caesar's name.
Lisa Lisa's tears flowed freely,
but their heartbroken cries of grief
were answered only by a cold silence.
Caesar was gone.
As they mourned him, they took
solace in one simple fact.
Though his body had died, his
soul would live on through them.
Rest in peace, Caesar Zeppeli.
In and around the lake.
Mountains come out of the sky.
They stand there.
24 before my love!
I'll be there.
You're really not impressing me.
I'm going to hug you to death.
We fight tonight under the full moon!
You have no tomorrow.
We'll face this fight together, Caesar?